[
    {
      "question": "What is the diameter <br> of a circle with radius 11?",
      "correctAnswer": "22",
      "options": [
        "24",
        "18",
        "21",
        "22"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the diameter <br> of a circle with radius 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "18",
      "options": [
        "21",
        "14",
        "15",
        "18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the diameter <br> of a circle with radius 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "1",
        "6",
        "7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the diameter <br> of a circle with radius 13?",
      "correctAnswer": "26",
      "options": [
        "23",
        "26",
        "21",
        "29"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the diameter <br> of a circle with radius 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "10",
        "8",
        "13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the diameter <br> of a circle with radius 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "18",
      "options": [
        "18",
        "19",
        "22",
        "13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the diameter <br> of a circle with radius 14?",
      "correctAnswer": "28",
      "options": [
        "30",
        "28",
        "31",
        "25"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the diameter <br> of a circle with radius 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "18",
      "options": [
        "17",
        "21",
        "16",
        "18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the diameter <br> of a circle with radius 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "6",
        "4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the diameter <br> of a circle with radius 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "13",
        "8",
        "5"
      ]
    }
  ]